<resources>
  <string name="package_name">com.eimantasn.spotypie</string>
  <string name="app_version_number">1</string>
  <string name="app_version_name">1</string>
  <string name="com.crashlytics.android.build_id">@string/app_version_number</string>

  <string name="app_name">SpotyPie</string>
  <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
  <string name="channelName">SpotyPie</string>
  <string name="ChannelId">987456123</string>
  <string name="channelDescription">SpotyPie hight quality music now possible</string>
  <string name="muse">Boasting eight acclaimed albums, 20 million sales and the most dazzling shows on earth, Muse are a triumph of millennial rock innovation and ambition. Formed in 1994 in Devon, they emerged with 1999’s Top 30 debut album Showbiz, showcasing their high art/hard rock blueprint. Buzz became cultdom with 2001’s double-platinum Origin Of Symmetry, an early masterpiece revolutionising modern rock with classical themes drawn from astronomy, theology and quantum physics. Steeped in grand melodic rock and introducing themes of psychological control and political manipulation, major breakthrough Absolution (2003) topped the UK chart, and 2006’s 4 million-selling, sci-fi themed Black Holes And Revelations made Muse a global phenomenon, breaking the US Top Ten and selling out Wembley Stadium. The Resistance (2009) pitched glam pop against rock symphonies, won a Grammy and hit #1 in 19 countries. In 2012 Survival, official anthem of the London Olympics, preluded sixth album The 2nd Law, tackling the Earth’s fuel crises. An onstage spectacle, Muse’s pioneering gigs featuring sci-fi sets, floating acrobats, UFOs and bouncing moons has been captured in concert films Hullabaloo (2002), HAARP (Live From Wembley Stadium) (2008), Live At Rome Olympic Stadium (2013) and Drones World Tour (2018), the ground-breaking show for 2015’s seventh album and US #1, Drones, a timely concept record about future warfare. 2018’s Simulation Theory examines the brighter side of technology with a world tour to follow.</string>

  <string name="favorite">Favorite</string>
  <string name="error_no_metadata">Unable to retrieve metadata.</string>
  <string name="browse_genres">Genres</string>
  <string name="browse_genre_subtitle">Songs by genre</string>
  <string name="browse_musics_by_genre_subtitle">%1$s songs</string>
  <string name="random_queue_title">Random music</string>
  <string name="error_cannot_skip">Cannot skip</string>
  <string name="error_loading_media">Error Loading Media</string>
  <string name="play_item">Play item</string>
  <string name="skip_previous">Skip to previous</string>
  <string name="play_pause">play or pause</string>
  <string name="skip_next">Skip to next</string>
  <string name="no_search_results">No search results.</string>

</resources>
